can I travel nightmare a massive storm unleashing snow and ice and rain and soon high winds across the country to screw up travel across the country inn already at the taco from millions on the move for Thanksgiving
我可以旅行的噩梦一个巨大的风暴释放冰雪和雨水，并在全国范围内搞砸了旅游全国各地的旅馆已经在塔科从数百万尽快大风在移动感恩节
control battle the fight over Obamacare and religious freedom in the Supreme Court
控制战斗过的Obamacare斗争和宗教自由在最高法院
double agents of secret government plan exposed
政府秘密计划的双重间谍暴露
how do you Western Guantanamo Bay prisoners in the spies and turn the moves
你怎么了西方关塔那摩囚犯在间谍和转动动作
how they are changing a Thanksgiving tradition
它们是如何改变传统的感恩节
headquarters in New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
总部设在纽约的NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
good evening is already tinnitus storm that stretches from the southern tip of Florida up to Nova Scotia and at its core which is a moving target right now
晚上好已经耳鸣风暴延伸，从佛罗里达州的南端可达新斯科舍，并在其核心是一个移动的目标，现在
it's dumping a ton of misery on several states the timing of the storm could not be worse because of what it does on the ground in the air to the business of getting around 700 flight delays already in this storm is just getting started
它倾倒一吨的痛苦上几个州风暴的时机不能因为是做什么的在地面上，在空中在这场风暴中已经得到约700航班延误的业务恶化才刚刚开始
the satellite picture of the nation from space shows the expanse of it tomorrow is the busiest travel day of the year 43 million Americans on the move
从太空国家的卫星图片显示的是明天的广阔是一年4300万美国人在移动中最繁忙的一天行程
and while the storm is churning in the eastern part of the country is affects of course will be felt all over is where we begin
而当风暴搅动在该国东部地区的影响，当然会觉得各地是我们开始
again tonight NBC stop Costello is out in it in Pittsburgh tonight I'm getting
今晚再次NBC停止科斯特洛今晚是出在它在匹兹堡我越来越
hi Brian effect in this area we used to have snow earlier today now is Dr Seuss born
喜在这方面，我们使用今天早些时候有小雪布莱恩效果现在是苏斯博士出生
showing extreme rain and cold out here for the ladies on hundred flight cancellations Nationwide we flew in today from Atlanta and we can tell you that it was a little bit of Roscoe and across the country everybody is doing today
表现出极度的雨水和寒冷在这里为女性上百航班取消全国性我们飞到今天在亚特兰大，我们可以告诉你，这是罗斯科的一点点，在全国每个人都在做的今天
the world's busiest airport in Atlanta
在亚特兰大世界上最繁忙的机场
cold driving range on the ramp for Robert cotton
在坡道罗伯特棉冷练习场
Griffin lay off and you know I know how long you going to be outside
格里芬裁员，你知道我知道你要去多久在外面
inside a Russian activity and just a handful delays and cancellations
里面一个俄罗斯的活动，只是极少数延误和取消
Atlanta
亚特兰大
tick tock my flight was among does delay
滴答滴答我的航班是不会延迟之间
waiting at the gate with me Stacy Danko trying to get home to Youngstown the
在门口和我一起等待斯泰西丹科想回家扬斯敦的
piano
计划
the way to didn't last long
以好景不长方式
Atlanta 90 minutes now head of Pittsburgh
亚特兰大90分钟现在头匹兹堡
the rain in Atlanta 400 winter landscape on a protein to Pittsburgh Airport blanket by about an inch of snow
雨在亚特兰大400冬季景观的一种蛋白质匹兹堡机场咧了约一英寸的雪
never been this battery travel from school after you're like a bad
从来没有从学校这种电池旅行你像一个糟糕的后
northern Michigan Ishida vyshla to a motor vehicle accident near Flint MI 75 percent lowers your Whitehall the dashboard cam
密歇根州北部石田vyshla至近密歇根弗林特机动车事故的75％降低你的白厅仪表盘凸轮
this truck jackknife Enid barely missing an already stopped car near Roanoke Virginia drivers permit with a quarter inch thick
用四分之一英寸这辆卡车折刀伊妮德勉强缺少一个已经停止的汽车附近弗吉尼亚州罗阿诺克允许司机厚
long Long Island New York super Franks in Del Rio have seen this before a holiday rush and treacherous roads
长期纽约长岛超弗兰克斯在德里奥前放假高峰和诡谲的道路已经看到了这
is it going to be emo
它是将要EMO
places that I would soon
地方，我会很快
and then factoring the weather
然后分解天气
probably going to create
大概要创建
very slow going and still 36 hours till Thanksgiving morning
很慢去，仍然36小时直到感恩节的早上
yeah the Fulton New York Pennsylvania bracing for a lot of snow in a lot of rain from quite a few parents concerned about the kids driving back from college get another thing to be concerned about Brian absolutely Tom Costello starting a saw from Pittsburgh Thompson
是啊富尔顿纽约宾夕法尼亚支撑了很多雪了很大的雨从不少家长关注孩子开车回从大学得到另一件事要关注布赖恩绝对汤姆·科斯特洛开始从匹兹堡汤普森锯
take a look at the life pictures of i-90 open
来看看的I-90的开放生活的图片
Buffalo where they don't scare easily in water soap the traffic is moving along the northern regions of the storm lyrics Peking 8 to 12 inches of snow before it's all over tonight meteorologist Jennifer Lopez
水牛在那里他们没有水肥皂容易吓唬流量沿风暴歌词北大8到12英寸的雪之前，一切都结束了今晚的气象学珍妮弗·洛佩兹北部地区移动
kind of knife to join us to look at where this is going in what's in store in genocider stand the winds on the back and are going to make for kind of a second wave of light problem
样的刀加入我们来看看这是怎么回事在什么商店在genocider站在后面的风和将要做出的那种淡淡问题第二波
exactly and that's when to come behind the system to win the head of the system make us up to 60 miles an hour in the northeast along the coastline when rain snow and Nealley the potential for tornadoes from Myrtle Beach to Jacksonville from Tallahassee to Tampa Florida tonight
正好，这时候来的系统背后胜制的头让我们到沿海岸线东北每小时60英里时，雨雪和Nealley今晚龙卷风从Myrtle Beach到杰克逊维尔从塔拉哈西到佛罗里达州坦帕的潜力
coffee to lace up and down the eastern seaboard computer forecast model track it through tonight is mainly rain from New York City download Washington CDC
咖啡花边上下东部沿海地区的计算机模型预测今晚通过跟踪它主要是由纽约市雨下载中华网华盛顿
back edges that snow ban you spoke about going to produce any work from 8 to 12 inches maybe even up to 18 inches of snow across portions of Lake Ontario
背部边缘，你谈到要出示任何工作从8到12英寸甚至高达18英寸的雪横跨安大略湖的部分雪禁令
here it is 6 a.m. Wednesday we still sing Big delays from New York City up into New England and more heavy rain moving through the region it starts to taper off around 6 o'clock in the evening on Wednesday but the damage weapon to be done by then
这里是11日上午6我们仍然唱大延迟从纽约市成新英格兰和更多的豪雨通过区域移动，它开始逐渐停止，6点钟左右，晚上在星期三，但伤害的武器是由完成然后
because the storm generation and how large is to
因为风暴的产生，以及如何大是
potential for rainfall 2 to 4 inches what is the reason effective 1260 12 inches of snow maybe even more than that of to 18 inches
潜在的降雨2到4英寸的原因是什么有效的1260 12英寸积雪甚至比18英寸以上
alisado the lakes upstate New York that extend back into a portion of Ohio as well as Pennsylvania how to turn off Windows right around 8 o'clock Thursday morning
alisado湖泊纽约州北部，可以回溯到俄亥俄州的一部分，以及宾夕法尼亚如何关闭Windows右键8时许周四上午
talking about just between 35 and 45 miles an hour from Boston
谈到刚刚在35和45英里的时速从波士顿
downtown New York City the course of the big Thanksgiving Day Parade is going to happen here in New York City on Thursday and there's a threshold in terms of the wind
纽约市中心的大感恩节游行的过程中是要在纽约市周四发生，并且有风的条件阈值
free close Macys will let everybody know where those large balloons will fly but definitely Buy Thanksgiving Day the weather is a la cama across the country can't wait for that
自由接近梅西将让大家知道这些大气球会飞到但绝对购买感恩节天气在全国各地一拉CAMA不能等待的
play everybody will need to be where they need to be by then genocide
发挥每个人将需要在那里他们需要通过再种族灭绝
The Weather Center will keep an eye on all about Janis thanks in other news Obamacare is back at the Supreme Court
气象中心将密切关注所有关于詹尼斯感谢其他新闻Obamacare的是回到了最高法院
this time the question is about religion and weather this new healthcare law require companies to offer contraceptives are justice course pond Pete Williams join us for my Washington bureau tonight with this latest challenge to the lobby creep
这一次的问题是关于宗教和天气这一新的医疗保健法律要求公司提供避孕药义场的水塘皮特·威廉姆斯加盟我华盛顿分社今晚这个最新挑战大堂蠕变
Brian good evening the Supreme Court has already rolled corporations have free speech rights now it has agreed to take a big question it is never answered before do private companies also have freedom of religion
布赖恩晚上好，最高法院已经推出公司拥有言论自由的权利现在它已经同意采取一切永远也不会回答一个大问题之前就私人公司也有宗教自由
the Oklahoma family that owns the Hobby Lobby with more than 550 arts and craft stores nationwide employed 13000 people does the company is found on religious principles
俄克拉何马家族拥有的业余爱好大堂有550多个艺术和工艺品商店全国就业13000人是否该公司正在对宗教原则发现
we believe how hard to believe that it is by God's grace improvision the Hobby Lobby has been successful
我们相信有多难相信这是神的恩典即兴的业余爱好大堂已经成功
therefore we see Don Hammond all that we do
因此，我们看到唐哈蒙德所有我们做的
what is providing insurance coverage for contraceptive measures like the morning after pill is the equivalent of paying for abortion violating is religious freedom
什么是提供保险的避孕措施，如避孕药后的早晨支付堕胎违反相当于是宗教自由
similar claim comes from a Pennsylvania woodworking company owned by a Mennonite family what does a company even
类似的索赔来自宾夕法尼亚州的木材加工公司，由门诺家族拥有什么对公司甚至
freedom of religion quarts are divided
宗教夸脱自由划分
everybody grease that's some organizations and companies have to have some religious freedoms take a church take a religious hospital the question we don't know is how far does that go to go to a craft store that happens to have religious owners
大家油脂这是一些组织和公司必须具备一定的宗教自由采取教堂参加宗教医院，我们不知道这个问题是在多大程度上确实是去赴一个工艺品商店，恰好拥有与宗教业主
religious institutions including churches in other non profit 7 exemptions from the requirement to provide contraceptive coverage for profit company space define a fail to comply
宗教机构，包括教堂等非营利7豁免的要求，提供避孕覆盖公司的利润空间中定义一个不遵守
freedom of religion is more than what you have in your head when you go to church services where you work at your family at your whole life that's exactly what
宗教信仰自由是​​比你在你的头上，当你去到哪里你在你的家庭工作，在你的整个生活，这正是教会服务
the framers of the Constitution have in mind start out
宪法的制定者心目中开始了
defending the law the Obama administration says nearly half of all pregnancies in the US are unintended costing healthcare 5 billion dollars a year in women's group say access to contraceptives is not just about birth control
捍卫法律，奥巴马政府说，在美国近一半的怀孕是意外医疗费用每年在妇女的5组十亿美元说获得避孕药不只是节育
oral contraceptives can reduce the risk of ovarian cancer BYOP to 50 percent so given that we have very few weapons against ovarian cancer this is very important for women
口服避孕药可减少卵巢癌BYOP的风险50％，以便给大家很少有武器，对卵巢癌，这是非常重要的女性
the coral probably hear this case in late March with the decision sometime before the end of June Bryant
珊瑚可能听到这种情况下，在3月下旬决定某个六月科比月底前
Williamson Rd C newsroom tonight Pizza X over seas in Afghanistan the deal for what happens after US combat troops leave next year
威廉姆森道中编辑部今晚比萨倍过海在阿富汗的成交为后美军作战部队发生的事情让明年
is subway on very shaky ground tonight Afghanistan's President Karzai upping the ante now making new demands in a meeting with National City
地铁是在非常不可靠的基础今晚阿富汗总统卡尔扎伊加大了赌注现已与全国城市会议上做了新的要求
visor Susan Rice saying he needs more concessions to let American troops stay in this country even on a non combat bases
遮阳板苏珊·赖斯说，他需要更多的让步，让美国军队留在这个国家，即使在非作战基地
Deal or No Deal the Americans still on the ground are in a top spot preparing to come home with so much work still
一掷千金的美国人还在地面上处于榜首准备回家与这么多的工作仍
head Archie foreign correspondent Richard Engel Hazal report tonight from forward operating base Cambury in eastern Afghanistan Richard the deep
头阿奇外国记者理查德·恩格尔Hazal从今晚在阿富汗东部理查德深前沿作战基地Cambury报告
good evening Brian this deal does seem to be in jeopardy in for American troops on outpost like this one and others like it
晚上好布赖恩这笔交易似乎是在危险中为美军前哨上像这样的和其他类似
its personal they are there family for trying to determine whether American forces will still have to reply to this country the future or whether the war in Afghanistan will truly be over next year
其个人他们在那里的家人试图确定是否美国军队仍然要回答这个国家未来或阿富汗战争是否将真正成为未来一年
the 10th Mountain Division Lock N Load and roll out
第10山地师锁N负荷和推出
heading down to what may be the most ionic border in the world
然后前往了可能是世界上最离子边界
Crossing to Pakistan
穿越巴基斯坦
the people in trucks are screened in all this is supposed to be one of the main roots out of Afghanistan for tons and tons of American supplies
人们在卡车被甄别这一切应该是一个主要根源出阿富汗的美国物资吨，吨
Pakistani clothes this portal crossing to us equipment is closed right now are the times its just too dangerous is a suicide attack your a few days ago
巴基斯坦服装这门道口至我们的设备被关闭，现在是时候它太危险的是自杀式袭击你的前几天
captain Kevin bolt is responsible for monitoring the crossing and worries what might happen if there's no US presidents and the Afghan troops training on ready to handle it
队长凯文螺栓负责监管交叉和担心可能会发生什么，如果没有美国总统和准备好处理它了阿富汗军队训练
definitely want to make sure we get the most out of bar the time in the blood sweat spent in a 9 in Afghan
一定要确保我们获得最大的酒吧时血液中的汗水在阿富汗一个9花
Major General James McConville from the hunter orange is the commander of about 10200 Eastern fence Tampa
从猎人的橙色少将詹姆斯·麦高伟是一个约10200东篱坦帕指挥官
chopper Reid to show progress bases McConnell shutdown the general from Boston ran 58 last bring it down to 13 the rest transfer to the Afghan army and police
菜刀里德来显示进度基地麦康奈尔关机波士顿一般跑58最后使其下降到13，其余移交给阿富汗军队和警察
11 by Afghan general tool
11阿富汗的一般工具
general have to look older
一般要显得更老
forces are still depended on McConville a whole lot
部队在高伟仍依赖一大堆
Need for the iPhone 4
需要为iPhone 4
uni5 the 10 mini day is it in Philadelphia
uni5的10个小日子是在费城
when does the final Francisco on the war in opened in 2001 closes
什么时候最终旧金山的战争在2001年开闭合
I don't know I don't I don't really know when the actual and is what I know is Ron appositive
我不知道，我不我真的不知道什么时候的实际，是我所知道的是罗恩同位语
appositive train right now to the Afghans haven't really Trupti for future
同位语的火车，现在的阿富汗人还没有真正Trupti为未来
US Afghan deal McConnell
美国阿富汗交易麦康奈尔
in the tens of thousands of men the command in limbo
在冷宫命令的数万人
the legacy of America's longest war
美国最长的战争遗留
are now open questions
现在是开放性问题
I was here say Karzai is probably negotiating a risk losing the most powerful biker this country is ever had Brian
我在这里说，卡尔扎伊可能是谈判有可能失去最强大的骑自行车的人这个国家曾经有过布莱恩
Richard Engel i from Afghanistan for us tonight Richard thank you and still have for us this evening secret agent supply
理查德·恩格尔我从阿富汗为我们今晚理查德·谢谢你，还有我们今天晚上特务供应
homeland name from The Beatles in a real life trailer exposed
从披头士乐队在现实生活中暴露拖车名称家园
hold the phone who is that
拿着手机那是谁
on the other end of the butterball hotline
在奶油热线电话的另一端
insta kind of thing we never know about while it's happening because we're not allowed to but tonight we are learning more about a secret areas quantanamo Bay called Penny Lane where after 9/11 the CIA took a sizable rest
斯塔样的，我们永远不会知道，而它的发生的事情，因为我们不允许但今晚我们正在学习更多关于秘密领域关塔那摩湾被称为竹篙巷，其中9/11事件后，美国中央情报局花了相当大的休息
we get more on the story from Archie foreign affairs correspondent Andrea Mitchell
我们得到更多的故事，从阿尔奇外交事务记者安德里亚·米切尔
hidden only a few hundred yards from the Guantanamo prison ministry of offices
隐藏办事处的关塔那摩监狱事工只有几百码
I top secret compound of colleges now abandoned by 10 years ago following 911 codenamed Penny Lane an ironic allusions
我顶院校的秘密化合物，现在已经废弃了10年前以下911研发代号为竹篙巷一个具有讽刺意味的​​典故
Beatles song just as get my was code named strawberry fields forever Penny Lane was more like home and then a magical mystery tour
甲壳虫乐队的歌曲，就像让我的是代号为永远的草莓地竹篙巷更像家，然后一个神奇的神秘之旅
first
第一
chapter and verse I can go back
引经据典，我可以回去
just as in the TV series the CIA try to turn hardcore 1 Tomo detainees in a double agents make them back into a car
就像在电视剧中央情报局试图把铁杆1托莫被拘留者在一个双重间谍让他们回到汽车
it would be responsible for the CIA or other intelligence organizations not to use these detainees to help protect United States against Detroit axe and that might well include using these operas as future agents to disrupt other attacks
这将是负责为中央情报局或其他情报机构不使用这些被拘留者，以帮助保护美国对底特律的斧头和可能以及包括使用这些歌剧作为未来剂扰乱对方攻击
the prisoners were in tights with Penny Lane special accommodations real beds and mattresses private kitchens in showers even pornography for those who ask and they were paid millions of dollars from a secret CIA account code Dame play
囚犯都在紧身衣与竹篙巷特殊的住宿真正的床和床垫私房菜淋浴间，甚至色情为那些谁问，并从中情局秘密帐户代码圣母院发挥他们支付了数百万美元
what day was always attract that was back Turnagain is a terrorist attack the US
什么日子总是吸引了回来特纳盖恩是恐怖分子袭击美国
I think it was very ill conceived program for them to think that because these are some very hardcore individuals and many homes have been released by both administrations have gotten back in to fight us in our allies unfortunately
我认为这是非常不适设想方案，他们认为，因为这些都是一些非常铁杆的个人和许多家庭已经发布由双方政府都变得早在争取我们在我们的盟友不幸
4 pics of a the CIA even considered income Pakistani former one time a prisoner's back to the US on student visa to track down a US territory that idea was apparently dropped in there is no evidence that any of this ever work
4照片的中央情报局甚至考虑收入巴基斯坦前一次囚犯回美国的学生签证追查一个美国境内的想法是明显回落的，没有证据表明任何这方面不断努力
my 2006 the entire project was abandoned Penny Lane remains 8 overgrown cottages
我在2006年，整个项目被放弃便士车道保持8杂草丛生的小屋
the desperate mindset after 9/11 Andrea Mitchell of NBC News Washington
之后的NBC新闻华盛顿9月11日安德烈·米切尔的绝望心态
and we're back in just a moment with something we said here on the air last night I got a response from Earth orbit
而我们又回到一会儿就好了的东西，我们在这里说的空气我昨晚从地球轨道的回应
CBS News an ounce today at some posing a leave of absence on 60 minutes correspondents Lara Logan and her producer max McClellan after their work
CBS新闻在一些冒充请假了60分钟的记者拉腊洛根和她的制作人Max麦克莱伦他们下班后的今天盎司
Benghazi was revealed to be wrong and based on a witness lied and internal CBS News report says that was Noah ball before the peace aired
班加西被发现是错误的，根据证人撒谎和内部CBS新闻报道说，挪亚球和平之前播出
and MSNBC Alec Baldwin have had what they are calling a neutral particle the way up late with Alec Baldwin on MSNBC has gone to bed earlier
和MSNBC亚历克·鲍德温有什么，他们都呼吁一个中性粒子一路上涨后期，亚历克·鲍德温在MSNBC已经早点休息
lasting only 5 episodes and is no more Baldwin received a rafter bad publicity after a tirade in some subsequent Runions with paparazzi
持久的只有5集，并没有更多的鲍德温收到椽不好的宣传在一些后续Runions长篇大论与狗仔队后
what princess is getting a lot of attention tonight for the mission statement gestation for the Catholic Church she would like to see in the future
什么公主得到了很多关注今晚的使命宣言酝酿天主教教会她想看到的未来
it was a kind of summary of a lot of things he's been saying lately he writes that the church must reform itself and pay more attention to the poor Ilsa wrote the church must quote abandon the complacent attitude that says we have always done it this way
这是一种很多事情，他一直说的总结最近他写道，教会必须自我改革，更加注重穷人伊尔莎写的教会必须引用摒弃自满的心态，说我们一直这么做的
notably he does go on to make clear the church doctrine on issues like abortion will not change elsewhere on the Pope schedule
尤其是他没有去弄清楚在诸如堕胎问题上教会的教义不会对教皇的时间表改变别处
this week was a meeting with who we should note showed up to meet the Pope 50 minutes late
本周是谁，我们应该注意到一个会议记录显示，以满足教皇50分钟晚
back in this country environmental officials are conducting a damage assessment after a towboat carrying 100 thousand gallons of fuel cell
早在这个国家的环保官员正在拖船运载十万加仑燃料电池后，进行损失评估
can the Mississippi River after striking something in the water along the way it's now leaking fuel in the water stretch a river in eastern I was close to bar traffic will they try to figure out how bad this weekend how to contain a
可以密西西比河一路走来它现在泄漏的燃油在水中舒展东部一条河流我很接近吧流量将他们试图弄清楚这多么糟糕的周末如何遏制惊人的东西在水中后，
because we have a reason to believe they would be watching us last night on this broadcast we ask the crew of the International Space Station to do is a big favor
因为我们有理由相信，他们会看着我们昨晚就这个广播，我们要求国际空间站的机组人员做的是一个大忙
and I try to take a picture of a house in Australia as they fly over head 17000 miles an hour giver take it looks like they're going to try to oblige today the NASA flight engineer on board the space station reply to whats on Twitter quotes
我试图采取的房子在澳洲的照片，因为他们在头上飞17000英里一个小时送礼者采取它看起来像他们要去尝尝今天迫使美国宇航局飞行工程师在船上的Twitter报价空间站回复什么
that is a tough picture to take but we will give it a try now the house in question is the Guinness record holder for the most Christmas lights at just over a half a million
这是一个艰难的图片采取，但我们会试试看现在房子的问题是在一百万半刚过吉尼斯纪录保持者为最圣诞灯
so we naturally figure it would be visible from space and we couldn't help but notice using one of the members many International Space Station web trackers
所以我们很自然地推测这将是从太空可以看到并使用的成员很多国际空间站的网络跟踪一个大家不禁通知
what are loftiest viewers have flown over Australia tonight since we been on the air so I hope you're high
什么是最崇高的观众纷纷今晚飞越澳大利亚，因为我们一直在空中，所以我希望你高
well she was born the daughter of hippies 43 years ago this coming Thursday so please join us in wishing happy Thanksgiving happy birthday and happy things
还有，她是43年前出生的嬉皮士的女儿本星期四，所以请加入我们，祝感恩节快乐生日快乐和幸福的事情
giving her name is happy Thanksgiving because hippies just used to think that way because otherwise she would have a name Tracy or something more conventional when we come back here tonight of Thanksgiving first real man talking Turkey
给她的名字是感恩节快乐，因为只是用那样认为吧，因为否则她将有一个名字特雷西或一些更常规的时候，才感恩节回来，今晚在这里的第一个真正的男人说话土耳其嬉皮士
finally here tonight 150 years ago today the President Lincoln sign the proclamation marking a national day of Thanksgiving and ever since then turkeys have been scared and the days since the invention of the
终于今晚在这里150年前的今天林肯总统签署宣言标志着感恩节为全国性节日，并从那时起火鸡一直害怕，以后的日子里的发明
phone people have been calling for the butterball hotline this year there is something new you might notice on the other end of the line we got that story tonight from NBC's Kevin Tibbles
手机的人一直在呼吁的奶油热线今年有新的东西你可能会注意到在我们得到了这个故事，今晚从NBC的凯文Tibbles线的另一端
Fox if your turkey is still in the freezer you're in big trouble don't panic talk turkey
狐狸，如果你的火鸡仍然在你的麻烦就大冰柜不要惊慌谈火鸡
4 users been helpful voice on the other end of the line to help with turkey baster fees Carol Miller doing it since the early days
4用户上线的另一端​​是有帮助的声音，以帮助土耳其巴斯特费卡罗尔·米勒这样做，因为创业初期
since 1984 and I think if he do that Mathis lake 29 years how is a sweet Bay vet
自1984年以来，我认为如果他这​​样做马西斯湖29年怎么是甜的海湾兽医
this year butterball has decided States high time someone else answered the phone to Butterball turkey taco help you yes man men doin just do the carving anymore butterball says 42 percent of the play a role in cooking turkey stew
今年奶油决定国家的时候别人接的电话，以奶油火鸡塔科帮助你是男人男人干什么只是做雕刻了奶油说该剧在烹调火鸡炖的作用42％
what's the typical male color say aside from help
什么是典型的男色说，除了帮助
on the first of all you got to talking down
所有你得到的第一个看不起他们的意思